<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ravi Sawlani</title><link>https://gravityvi.co.in/</link><description>Recent content on Ravi Sawlani</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Ravi Sawlani</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gravityvi.co.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A very new blog</title><link>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/a-very-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/a-very-new-blog/</guid><description>sample goes here.</description></item><item><title>Finding Elements From Element - xpath paradox</title><link>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/finding-elements-from-element-xpath-paradox/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 16:12:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/finding-elements-from-element-xpath-paradox/</guid><description>Xpath Xpath is a locator strategy used to find elements on a page. XPath stands for XML path. XPath uses path expressions to select nodes from documents.
Usage In Automation Scripts Xpath is a locator strategy used to find elements on a page. XPath stands for XML path. XPath uses path expressions to select nodes from documents.
Finding Elements from Element There are a lot of different approaches for this purpose in different frameworks.</description></item><item><title>Ravi Sawlani</title><link>https://gravityvi.co.in/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:48:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://gravityvi.co.in/about/</guid><description>By profession, I am a software developer but beyond that, I have a deep fascination for all things tech.
I enjoy solving problems and making solutions accessible for everyone Being a part of open source projects is very important to me and I try and do my part as a developer in the open-source team at BrowserStack.
In past, I have worked as a backend developer in SenseHawk, helped them develop a service that helps to create customizable forms and generate useful reports based on submissions made to the form.</description></item><item><title>Work From Home Setup</title><link>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/work-from-home-setup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 16:12:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://gravityvi.co.in/posts/work-from-home-setup/</guid><description>Background Growing as a kid in a generation where computers and laptops were not so common, I was always fascinated and wanted to surround myself with digital devices. I still remember I had my first computer when I was in fifth grade. Now working as a software developer has its advantages, one of them being, you work with cool digital devices.
Setup Due to the pandemic, most of the software developers are working from home.</description></item></channel></rss>